[{"answer": "Liar", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Sorry", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "This is what we do", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Maybe I should see...", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'm fine, thank you", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "  You listen to me.  The only reason I'm letting you be part of this is 'cause you got the helicopter and the rada", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I do  like you", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "It's too dangerous fo", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You flew up here because your bos", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Jesus Christ!", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What are  doing?", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You're crawling around like ", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "A spring trap", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "In his defense, every primitive culture known to man deified them. He's a mythology professor, he thinks crocs are divine conduits", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "It's to make you  him, with understanding comes tolerance. Too bad they don't put proverbs in Twinkies, my load would be lighter", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Two years married, divorced, used to be a lawyer, quit, I'm still waiting on his sperm count", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "As if.  Will you miss me", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "  He was an Ind", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Scales were oval.  It was an crocodile", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " At school they'd always say", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " He never said", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": ".  I keep getting hit with heads", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You calm down", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "The more he thrashes, the better", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "We're ready", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Where is he?", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Back us in a little, we need to get a shot", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " You're gonna be okay", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah, you got bit.  I'm gonna fix it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Okay", "docId": "lake-placid.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well... I got stuff to pack up and..", "qsentId": 32}]